♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪ ♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪ ♪ I'M HOLDIN' ON A ROPE ♪ ♪ GOT ME TEN FEET OFF THE GROUND ♪ ♪ AND I'M HEARIN' WHAT YOU SAY ♪ ♪ BUT I JUST CAN'T MAKE A SOUND ♪ ♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪ ♪ YOU TELL ME THAT YOU NEED ME ♪ ♪ THEN YOU GO AND CUT ME DOWN ♪ ♪ BUT WAIT ♪ ♪ YOU TELL ME THAT YOU'RE SORRY ♪ ♪ DIDN'T THINK I'D TURN AROUND ♪ ♪ YOU SAY ♪ ♪ THAT IT'S TOO LATE TO APOLOGIZE ♪ ♪ IT'S TOO LATE ♪ ♪ HEY, HEY, HEY... ♪ ♪ I SAID, IT'S TOO LATE TO APOLOGIZE ♪ ♪ IT'S TOO LATE ♪ ♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪ ♪ OH ♪ ♪ OH OH ♪ ♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪ ♪ TAKE ANOTHER CHANCE ♪ ♪ TAKE A FALL, TAKE A SHOT FOR YOU ♪ ♪ OH, I NEED YOU LIKE A HEART NEEDS A BEAT ♪ ♪ BUT IT'S NOTHING NEW ♪ ♪ YEAH, YEAH ♪ ♪ I LOVED YOU WITH A FIRE ♪ ♪ AND NOW IT'S TURNIN' BLUE ♪ ♪ AND YOU SAY ♪ ♪ SORRY LIKE THE ANGEL ♪ ♪ HEAVEN LET ME THINK WAS YOU ♪ ♪ BUT I'M AFRAID ♪ ♪ IT'S TOO LATE TO APOLOGIZE ♪ ♪ IT'S TOO LATE ♪ ♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪ ♪ I SAID, IT'S TOO LATE TO APOLOGIZE ♪ ♪ IT'S TOO LATE ♪ ♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪ ♪ WHOA OH ♪ ♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪ ♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪ ♪ IT'S TOO LATE TO APOLOGIZE ♪ ♪ IT'S TOO LATE ♪ ♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪ ♪ I SAID, IT'S TOO LATE TO APOLOGIZE ♪ ♪ IT'S TOO LATE ♪ ♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪ ♪ I SAID IT'S TOO LATE TO APOLOGIZE ♪ ♪ YEAH... ♪ ♪ HEY, HEY, HEY ♪ ♪ I SAID, IT'S TOO LATE TO APOLOGIZE ♪ ♪ YEAH ♪ ♪ I'M HOLDIN' ON A ROPE ♪ ♪ GOT ME TEN FEET ♪ ♪ OFF ♪ ♪ THE GROUND ♪